(clicks tongue)
(Amy:)How do you know that?
(Penny:)Oh, Leonard mumbles it when
he wants sex to last longer.
(Claire:)Hey, Raj.
(Raj:)Hey, Claire.
Good, you're here.
(Raj:)Guys, this is
my friend Claire.
(Raj:)We're casually dating,
and there's no need
(Raj:)for any further questions
about it.
(Leonard:)Would you like
a glass of wine?
I said no questions!
SHELDON: And last
but not least,
(Sheldon:)this is one that I like to call
Star Wars Toast because...
(Sheldon:)it has a light side
and a dark side.
(Sheldon:)All righty, it's time for
Dungeons & Dragons!
(Sheldon:)Dungeons & Dragons.
(Bernadette:)That sounds about right.
(Sheldon:)You're gonna
enjoy this.
(Sheldon:)I designed it
especially for you.
(Bernadette:)Okay, but just for a little bit.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I have a feeling
that once you start,
(Sheldon:)you're not gonna want to
or be allowed to stop.
(Penny:)All right.